

### CONTACT ME AT

♥ ^ 1400 Hi Line Dr. APT 2013 Dallas, TX 75207 julian@rodriguez.org



@julianrodriguezit



817-422-3584

#### PERSONALITY TRAITS

Master of multi-tasking

Quick to learn on the fly

Open to fearless feedback

Plan - Collab - Execute

Obsessed with the details

Teamwork-Oriented

## N O T A B L E <u>A C H I E V E M</u> E N T S

- Workfront Core Partner
  Certification
- Workfront Fusion/Azuqua
  Certification
- Full consultation, discovery, implementation, and deployment for AT&T Creative Services New York

# JULIAN RODRIGUEZ

## SOLUTIONS CONSULTANT

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I've worn a lot of hats throughout my professional journey! While most of my experience has been customer-facing experience in Sales and Support, I have a strong passion for Sales-Enablement and being a part of the team that architects the systems that make teams successful.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Account Executive**

Peloton Interactive | October 2019 - Current

- High-Velocity sales from inbound chatters on our website and direct phone lines.
- Providing a warm and friendly experience despite the medium (chat/phones) for potential new members

## **Solutions Consultant**

IO Integration | July 2018 - October 2019

- Demonstrate business acumen while being the liaison between DevOps and Client
- Provide in-depth discovery and documentation for delivery
- Deploy architected solutions for both on-premesis and cloud

#### EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

## University of Texas at Austin

Bachelor's Degree in Government | 2013 - 2018 Minor in Rhetoric and Writing

- Studying Government was a key period in my life that turned me into the person I am today. It opened my mind to the experiences of people across the world, and how their societies operate on a human level.
- Competed in US and Global Policy Debate Championships
- University Investors Association Member